Maid suits you too.
メイドも似合いますね
is that so?
そうですか?
It's cute.
可愛いね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Try waving your hand a little.
ちょっと手とか振ってみてよ
It keeps shaking me.
ずっと振ってくれるんだね
Will you stop?
やめます?
It's cute.
可愛いですね
I'm calling you.
呼んじゃってます
Are you calling me?
呼んでるんですか?
Just fill up your cosplay.
ちょっとコスプレを満たさにね
May I call you?
呼んじゃっていいですか?
nice to meet you.
初めまして
She kind of looks like the girl I was trying to attract at the cabaret club earlier,
なんかさっきキャバクラの呼び込みやってた女子に似てるけど、
Is it you?
本人ですか?
No, it's not.
いや、違います
Is it cute?
可愛いかな?
I haven't done it.
やってないです
Aren't your hands so beautiful?
すごい手も綺麗じゃない?
It's wonderful to see people who do everything right down to their fingertips.
指先までしっかりやってる人って素敵ですよね
is that so?
そうですか?
Now, like this, like this,
これでこうやって、なんかこうやって、
Is this how you do it?
こうやってやったりするの?
You seem to like it, don't you?
なんか好きそうだね、あなたね
Does it look like that?
そんな風に見えます?
I can see it.
見えます
Very.
非常に
Do you dislike it?
お嫌いですか?
I like it.
好きですよ
You can easily greet people in a foreign style.
軽く外国式の挨拶できます
It's definitely erotic.
間違いなく、エロいね
Will the usage below change?
下の使い方変わらんか?
Easy to switch on
スイッチ入りやすい
hey.
ね
That way, he'll hold your hand properly.
そ りゃ、ちゃんと手絡めてくれるんだ
Go ahead and hate it.
さあ、お嫌いに
Is this so?
こうですか?
It's facing straight up.
真上向いてるよ
My shoulder rang.
肩が鳴っちゃった
Well then, we're together.
じゃあ、一緒だ
We're together.
一緒だね
Can you take me here?
こっち乗せるでしょ?
I rode his punches.
彼のパンチに乗ってきたよ
There's a lot of pussy gel stuck together.
マンコジェル、いっぱいくっついてるよ
Pussy gel.
マンコジェル
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいよ
Please give me this punch.
このパンチ、頂戴
No, no, no.
ダメ、ダメ、ダメ
I want to go inside this and go home.
これ、入って帰りたいんだけど
No, no, no.
ダメ、ダメ、ダメ
I want to see every inch of you.
あなたのこと、隅々まで見たいんだけど
I want you to open your pussy a little.
マンコ、ちょっと開いてほしいんだよね
You're good at it.
上手じゃん
Is it usually open?
普段から開いてるの?
It's not open.
開いてないよ
Isn't it open?
開いてないの?
Amazing pink.
すごいピンク
It's embarrassing to see so much.
そんなに見たら恥ずかしいですよ
I've been watching this for a long time.
ずっと見てたよ、これ
Just do this, don't put anything in here.
こういうことしといてさ、 ここに何も入らないでって
Are you going home?
帰っちゃうのとか
picture?
え?
Is that lonely?
それは寂しいの?
picture?
え?
What should I put in it?
何入れるんですか?
何入れようか
Should I put a ballpoint pen in there?
ボールペンとか入れとく?
Ballpoint pen?
ボールペン?
Is that not okay?
そんな、そんなんじゃダメ?
Can I put a ballpoint pen in it?
ボールペン入れちゃうの?
My pussy is open, even more.
マンコ、開いたよ、更に
Open, open.
開いた、開いた
It's not a ballpoint pen.
ボールペンじゃないもん
What is this?
これ、何これ?
Wow.
うわ ー
It became lukewarm.
ぬるみになっちゃった
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
The soup was dripping into the soup as well.
おつゆがお汁の方にも垂れてたの
I like being licked.
舐められるの好きなんだ
What should we do about this?
これさ、どうする?
I'm about to put it on, let it dry.
フーって着かけてさ、 乾かしちゃうか、
Should I lick it and get it wet?
舐めて濡らすか
Is it better to paint?
塗れるほうがいい?
Is it better to dry?
乾くほうがいい?
It's amazing how much you can drink.
ちんちん飲めるのすごい
You like it, right?
好きでしょ?
What do you think?
どうだろう
He's healing really well right now.
今、すごい癒してくっこしてるからね
I was watching from 1 o'clock instead of 12 o'clock.
12時どころか、1時の方から見ちゃってる
It's too late now, but it's Matson.
今更だけど、メートソンだよね
Yeah, that's a little bit like that.
うん、ちょっとそうだよ
Can you please tell me?
言ってみてもらっていい?
picture?
え?
what?
何?
Please say it, master.
言えてください、ご主人様
picture?
え?
It's so embarrassing.
そんなに恥ずかしい
I dare you to say something like that in English now.
そんな英語っぽいやつをあえて 今、
Do you want me to say it?
言ってほしいの?
You're eating your legs.
足食いになっちゃってるじゃん